sportanddev.org 2019-04-26

# Privacy Policy | sportanddev.org

This Privacy Policy covers the International Platform on Sport & Development (the ‘Platform’)’s treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on the Platform website or when you use the Platform’s services.

2\. Information Collection and Use  
The Platform collects personally identifiable information when you register as a Team Player. When you register with the Platform, we ask for your name, e-mail address, city and country, and we ask that you locate yourself on the interactive map. We also ask you for a short bio describing yourself and we ask that you describe your areas of interest in the field of Sport & Development. 

By providing your information to us, you are giving your permission for your personal information to be made freely and publicly available via the internet to any internet user accessing the website (your password is not shown to other members; your email address is not displayed on the site but members will be able to send messages to you using web-based contact forms). A user will be able to view your information in a web browser but will not be able to change your information displayed on the website. Your information could be passed in this way to third parties in any country worldwide. If you do not wish to allow this type of access to your information, please do not enter your information.

The website administrators also have access to your personal information, but they will only use this information to contact you for account management purposes, or to inform you of changes to the website. We will not share your information with other organisations.

3\. Information Sharing and Disclosure  
We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.   
You can contact us directly with questions or comments regarding the services or to request additional information by writing to [info@sportanddev.org](https://www.sportanddev.org/en/void%280%29%3B/%2A1220880655797%2A/). By writing to us, we require you to provide certain personal information (such as your email address) so that we may respond to your inquiry.

For distribution purposes, you also provide personally identifiable information if you request materials from us. We may also use this information to determine the level of interest our products and services. We may use your personal information to get in touch with you regarding the status of your online requests for services or any additional information you requested. 

We may use your personal information to contact you regarding additional services and features or requesting your feedback about your experience with our site.

4\. Cookies  
The Platform may set and access the Platform cookies on your computer, used to identify your member account and to allow for the proper functioning of the web site and its services.

5\. Editing your Information and Preferences  
As a registered member, the Platform gives you the ability to edit your Information and Preferences at any time, including whether you would like to receive correspondence from the Platform.

6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy  
We reserve the right to amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting an announcement.
